{
    "subject": "resource/Ferret_Music",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributingCompany",
    "object": "resource/Fontana_Distribution",
    "human_readable": "Ferret Music is distributed by Fontana Distribution.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9535983204841614,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ferret Music and Fontana Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8947980403900146,
            "question": "Is Fontana Distribution involved in music distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8797390460968018,
            "question": "Who distributes Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445066809654236,
            "question": "Which band or artist's music is distributed by Fontana Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378584980964661,
            "question": "Does Ferret Music have a distribution agreement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8338814377784729,
            "question": "Name a music label distributed by Fontana Distribution."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7618247866630554,
            "question": "What is the name of the distribution company for Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7553718090057373,
            "question": "Who are some other artists distributed by Fontana Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5841618776321411,
            "question": "What type of content does Fontana Distribution handle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34210142493247986,
            "question": "What does it mean for music to be 'distributed'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferret Music is distributed by Fontana Distribution.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6958_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of content does Fontana Distribution handle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6958_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other artists distributed by Fontana Distribution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6958_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the distribution company for Ferret Music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6958_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6958_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is asking whether the statement \"Ferret Music is distributed by Fontana Distribution\" is supported by the provided context information.\n\nFrom the context information, we can see that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6958/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt, it says \"Ferret recently started an imprint called New Weathermen Records.  Warner Music Group's Alternative Distribution Alliance acquired a stake in Ferret Music in August, 2006, and as a result is currently distributed by Fontana Distribution, Alternative Distribution Alliance and eOne Music.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6958/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt, it says \"Distributors Fontana Distribution, Entertainment One Distribution, Alternative Distribution Alliance\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6958/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt and 19.txt, it says similar information about Ferret Music being distributed by Fontana Distribution.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Warner Music Group's Alternative Distribution Alliance acquired a stake in Ferret Music and that as a result, it is currently distributed by Fontana Distribution. Therefore, the statement \"Ferret Music is distributed by Fontana Distribution\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}